Analia Giachini

Full Stack Developer

Aarhus - Dinamarca (+54) 50295996 analiagiachini@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/analiagiachini/?locale=en_US https://github.com/AnaliaGiachini

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Full Stack developer with experience in Front End and Back End development. My technical skills include the use of JavaScript, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, agile methodologies, Git, and data structure.

I am practical, organized and I have an agile learning which allows me to be productive when creating dynamic, efficient and attractive web applications. I value good communication and the possibility of continuous learning that allows me to grow and succeed in the projects in which I participate.

English level: A2 +.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - Countries

March. 23 - April. 22

Academic experience.

Henry Bootcamp, Cordoba, Argentina.

Design and development of a Web Application about countries around the world. It allows you to search for countries using their name. When selecting the country, information such as the name, its flag, its capital, its continent and other relevant data is displayed.

You can create a tourist activity for the countries, it also contains orders and filters by different criteria such as alphabetically ascending or descending, by amount of population, by continents and tourist activities.

Front: React, Redux Back: Node, Express

Base de datos: PostgreSQL y Sequelize.

https://github.com/AnaliaGiachini/PI-Countries-main

Full Stack Web Developer - Salvando Huellas

April. 23 - May. 23

Academic experience.

Henry Bootcamp, Cordoba, Argentina.

Design and development of a Web Application for a Canine Shelter, in this application you can generate an adoption request for the different dogs that are in the shelter. You can view them through the different filters such as size, age and sex. In addition, the application has an e-commerce, a donation section, user registration and administrator management, among other features.

Front: React, Redux Back: Node, Express

Base de datos: PostgreSQL y Sequelize.

https://github.com/AnaliaGiachini/PF-Salvando-Huellas

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Manager May. 17 - October. 21

Municipalidad de Jesús María, Córdoba, Argentina

Control and Update of the DB of Suppliers and articles.

Purchasing Administrative Assistant

May. 17 - October.. 21

Municipalidad de Jesús María, Córdoba, Argentina

• Supplier management - Current account - Billing - Stock.

Purchasing Manager

2006 - May. 2017

Ceramicos Margarita SRL, Córdoba, Argentina.

• Supplier Management, Current Account, Billing, Stock, Cash and Banks.

IT support technician

2005 - July. 2006

K.I Computación, Córdoba, Argentina.

- Maintenance and Repair of Hardware (PCs and printers).
- Installation and configuration of Networks (Windows) and Software.

TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, CSS, HTML. **Tools:** Git, Slack. **Agile:** Scrum.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 700 hours of theoretical-practical course. jan. may. 2023.
- Front End Developer. Centro de e-Learning UTN FRBA.
 jan. 2021 mar. 2021
- Fifth full year de Ingeniería de Sistemas. Instituto Universitario Aeronáutico. 2001 - 2006.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Fluent bilingual or native
- English A2 +. https://www.efset.org/cert/vYgebR
- Italian A2.